(On a particularly sweltering day in August)
We're in Dongjak-gu.
They're giving us tasty refreshments today.
- Did you have breakfast?
- I did.
What did you have?
Well, I had some rice with eggs...
and japchae.
- So...
- You have a nice breakfast.
- You had japchae for breakfast?
- My gosh.
- My breakfast is always nice.
- Really?
(He had quite the breakfast.)
I enjoyed my breakfast.
People rarely get to have japchae for breakfast.
We're filming the show...
- in the middle of the day.
- I see.
- The fact that they don't know...
- I'm nervous.
We're coming...
is kind of crazy.
I mean, they need to be prepared in some way.
But Jae Seok seems to manage without any preparation.
Really? That's fascinating.
- I think it's this way.
- This way.
I see. What a unique location for a cafe.
Wait. This is quite sudden.
- Is that Hae In?
- Wait. Sung Tae!
- Who's that?
- Hae In.
- What?
- Hello.
(With his youthful looks, )
(this young guy made the hearts of many older women flutter.)
(With one gesture...)
(and one line, )
(the viewers were instantly won over.)
(A top-tier actor with incredible genre versatility)
(Actor Jung Hae In)
(The biggest villain in "Squid Game" that kept the entire world on edge)
(He can pull off playing a gangster role...)
(and a detective role.)
(Actor Heo Sung Tae can even pull off playing a romantic role.)
(The two lead actors from "Our Sticky Love")
- Hello.
(Happy to see him)
- Sung Tae.
- My gosh.
- Mr. Lawyer.
- My goodness.
- What's going on?
- Sung Tae.
- Let's sit down.
- Okay.
Hae In.
- It's been a while, Hae In.
- Gosh.
We met briefly when we were both filming.
- Remember?
- Yes. We did.
- I was filming an SBS drama.
- Yes.
- He was filming his new drama then.
- Oh, right.
- He was filming in the next studio.
- It was at the same company.
- I went to say hello to him.
- Oh, right.
He rushed over and said hello.
- Gosh, he's one polite guy.
- Yes. My gosh.
I didn't know you guys were joining us today.
I wanted to ask him to take on my case.
- He played a ghost in the drama.
- Oh, right.
- You were both in the drama.
- In "Phantom Lawyer."
- "Phantom Lawyer."
- He had a really tough role.
- Why?
- He was in Episodes 1 and 2.
- I see.
- He played a ghost,
so he had to film the same scenes twice...
because he had to be seen and then disappear.
He was constantly strapped into wires.
I had the most fun experience while filming the drama.
I had to be up in the air.
I didn't have any special equipment. I just delivered my lines.
(He had to make it look like he was floating.)
- You had to do that? I get it.
- Yes, I had to do it.
- His character was floating.
- You were floating in the air.
- That was a new kind of experience.
- That's...
(He's pretending that he's floating.)
(Floating)
One day, they gave him a gym ball.
He got the gym ball and sat on it.
- Right. I know.
- So...
he had to pretend he was floating.
That was a new experience.
- I knew that Hae In's new drama...
- Yes.
- was going to air soon.
- Right.
- The title is "Our Sticky Love."
- Yes.
- So...
- Is it called sticky...
because you can't be separated?
- My gosh.
- I see.
- Of course.
- I knew it.
- That's the meaning behind it?
- Yes.
- It's sweet and sticky like taffy.
- It's sweet too.
- It's sticky like taffy.
I watched the trailer.
She has amnesia in the drama.
Right.
She has amnesia.
And I'm insisting that I'm her boyfriend.
In a way, I'm tricking her into falling in love with me.
(A prosecutor loses her memory while chasing a case.)
(Jang Tae Ha, the boyfriend)
(Tangled between the truth and secrets)
(A sweet and suspenseful romance with an amnesia twist)
(It's available on the streaming website.)
But that sounds like a nice deal.
- She doesn't have any memory.
- Okay.
One day, she just wakes up.
Hae In comes and tells her he's her boyfriend.
- Right.
- Yes.
So you're the villain...
in their love story, right?
- You're the villain.
- Yes.
I make a sticky mess.
- Watch your pronunciation.
- I see.
- He's a supervillain.
- A villain?
- Really?
- It's been a while.
It's been three years since I last played...
- Really?
- a villain.
I've been mostly playing detectives.
It felt just like riding a bicycle, right?
- But the thing is...
- It was easy, wasn't it?
When we started filming and running lines...
in the beginning, it didn't hit me.
Then we did a scene where blood splattered on my face.
Once blood splashed on my face,
I thought, "This is it."
So this is what I said to the director.
"I'm getting the hang of it now."
- I was on fire after that.
- You were getting the hang of it.
It was really fun.
He played the villain.
We're in...
We're in Dongjak-gu...
- near Boramae Park, right?
- Boramae Park.
- We passed Sangdo-dong.
- Right.
Who has ties to this neighborhood?
- Hae In lived here for a long time.
- It's Hae In.
I briefly lived here.
I live in Gyeonggi Province now.
You moved?
- I recently moved.
- Recently?
- You recently moved?
- Yes.
So...
when we were filming the drama, we lived close to each other.
- Really?
- Yes.
- So this is your neighborhood?
I've been living here for over 30 years.
- I see. Really?
- It's been about 30 years.
I did my military service around here.
- Where?
- I was in the Air Force.
He's mentioning that again.
- What?
- He always brings up...
his military service and Sejong University.
- We're near Boramae Park.
- Come on.
There's an Air Force base.
- I was in the Air Force. So...
- I mean, I know that.
Can't I mention that I was in the Air Force?
His nickname is Jong.
But I didn't bring up the university today.
Seriously. The university...
We shouldn't go to Gwangjin-gu.
They should give you an award.
No one has put Sejong University on the map quite like Yeon Seok...
besides Sejong the Great.
- You know what's strange?
- I'm serious.
I got invited...
- for a Hangul Day event.
- Right?
- See?
- I...
Sejong University ought to do something nice for him.
Anyway, you've been living around Boramae Park...
- for 30 years.
- I've been here for a long time.
You must've gone to a local high school then.
Yes. I went to elementary, middle, and high schools...
in this neighborhood.
This is your hometown then.
I grew up in Daebang-dong.
- Gosh.
- Daebang-dong.
- Daebang-dong...
- My base was in Daebang-dong.
Across Military Manpower Administration.
- Well, yes.
- I'm serious.
- There's an Air Force base.
- Yes.
But you don't live here anymore, right?
- I still have ties here.
- Okay.
My parents still live here.
- I see. They live here.
- So you go back and forth.
- Yes. I go back and forth.
- Your parents...
I used to go to Boramae Park before my career took off.
There's a boxed meal takeout place...
in the basement of a department store.
- I know the one.
- I bought a boxed meal...
- and ate it at the park by myself.
- Did you practice at the park?
I remember doing that.
When I sometimes come here and want to go to a good restaurant,
I remember Hae In and think about asking him for recommendations.
- I hold myself back and never ask.
- Why not?
- Why not? You should ask.
- You can ask.
I mean, he's busy.
I hearted a lot of places...
- on Google Maps.
- Right. I saw a lot of hearts.
- I see. The ones you saved?
- Yes. I saved a lot of places.
- A tteokbokki stall and so on.
- Then...
do you like going to famous restaurants?
I like going to restaurants.
- Hae In likes doing that.
- I see.
- Yeon Seok and Hae In...
- Let's go to a good one today.
Right.
We don't have to worry about food today.
What if you have to wait in line for over 30 minutes?
Would you wait?
- It's Friday today.
- Oh, right.
When you see a line, do you give up instead of waiting in line?
I... Right.
(Satisfied)
You don't wait in line?
- No.
- You have a list, but don't wait?
I have other places saved too.
He goes to another restaurant he has saved.
(That's the way to go.)
I don't get stressed out...
when a plan changes.
- Your MBTI type ends with P.
- Yes.
- What about you?
- Really?
- Mine ends with P too.
- I see.
Let's say I go to a famous restaurant...
and there's a long line.
- Do you...
- I eat at a convenience store...
if there's one nearby.
- I do that too.
- Really? I see.
- I'm not like that.
- Okay.
What about you, Sung Tae? What's your type?
My type is F.
No.
Does it end with J or P?
- Which one?
- It's J.
- You're so clueless.
- I'm sorry.
- "My type is F."
- It's INFJ.
Why don't you say your type is X?
Did you get an F in school or what?
- You know what J stands for, right?
- Yes. They plan things.
(Hold on.)
Type P also plans things.
I didn't call you guys out.
We just don't like to plan things.
- Right.
- Yes.
- Anyway, we must get going today.
- Let's go.
All right. Let's go and meet...
the Whenever Friend from Dongjak-gu.
Her name is Yoon Na Ra.
- Na Ra.
- Yes.
"I'm Dongjak-gu Fire Fist and want to give a boost..."
"to our champion..."
"who is set to embark on a new journey."
They must be boxers.
- Fire Fist.
- Right?
"I'd like to invite the hosts..."
"of Whenever Possible to our first sanctuary,"
"steeped in sweat and memories for the final round."
- Is it a gym?
- "Champion."
"Final round." "Fire Fist."
- Then it has to be a boxing gym.
- Do we have to box?
- A boxing gym?
- It must be a boxing gym.
Do you box, Sung Tae?
- In our drama, - Do you box, Hae In?
- I play a former boxer.
- I...
But my character quit boxing...
- and joined the gang.
- I see.
He also plays a former boxer.
- I also play a former boxer.
- He plays a former boxer.
- Both of you play former boxers?
- So both of our characters...
have something to do with boxing in the drama.
I once played a boxer a long time ago too.
- Really?
- It was a high school student.
- Have you done any boxing before?
- Me?
There was a segment called "Tomorrow's Champion."
- Shim Hyung Rae was in it.
- Wait.
- What?
- I loved that segment.
- You liked that segment?
- Yes.
You know the sound he made? That.
It was called "Tomorrow's Champion." Shim Hyung Rae was in it.
- How do I know that?
- It was a popular segment.
- Hae In doesn't know it.
- I know it very well.
- Of course, Sung Tae knows.
- I know too.
(Responding right away)
- His nickname was The Hisser.
- Right.
Anyway, let's go. Where's the place?
- We must be there by 12:30pm.
- We can get going now.
Let me check the distance.
- A boxing game?
- It takes 15 minutes on foot.
Fifteen minutes?
- Fifteen minutes on foot.
- Okay.
- Let's walk there.
- Okay. Shall we?
My gosh.
- Goodness.
- The air feels incredibly hot.
You know what?
Every year, summer's getting hotter.
- Right.
- Right?
Back in the day, the highest temperature...
- would be around 34°C.
- Exactly.
- But now...
- It hit 40°C this year.
- Daegu...
- It's over 40°C in the south.
- It's 40°C in Daegu.
- Right.
Gosh, this is a huge problem.
- Hey, we can't.
- Stay on the left.
Jae Seok, hold on.
- Yeon Seok.
- Hold on.
We must go with a different option. This is...
We're feeling the heat and all.
But we're the only ones walking on the street.
- No one's out.
- Hold on.
- Today...
- The heatwave alert was issued.
Jae Seok, do you want to get on a bus...
even if it's just for one stop?
- Let's do it.
- A bus stop is across the street.
- We should ride the bus.
- Great.
- Let's ride it just for one stop.
- That sounds good.
(Looking up the bus route)
My gosh. It's scorching hot today.
(Glancing)
You know what?
Only you have a fan.
Oh, this?
My fan from Chiang Mai sent this to me. Thank you.
- Really? Did you know?
- Hello, Chiang Mai.
There's a handheld fan that blows cold air.
- Right.
- It's right here.
- It cools the air.
- It blows cold air.
This fan doesn't suit your character in the drama.
But I always...
(He shows off his scary looks in the drama.)
(But in real life, he just hates the heat.)
- Is that the bus stop?
- Hold on.
(They arrive at the bus stop before they melt.)
- Is this the bus stop, Yeon Shik?
- Yes, it is.
What's the bus number?
I think that's the one. Bus 5516.
- Is it coming?
- It's here.
- Perfect timing.
- Two stops?
- Yes, two stops.
- Gosh, it's summer.
- Can you tag me in?
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Yes.
(Fully air-conditioned)
- This is nice.
- Two stops. Gosh, my back.
(Oh, we can finally breathe now.)
- This is so nice.
- My gosh.
Gosh, it's nice.
It's only 15 minutes away on foot, but there's no way we can walk.
Luckily, the bus turns right over there.
- That's good.
- We'll get off at Seongdae Market.
We just need to walk three more minutes.
Your quick decision-making was great.
- Seriously.
- Right?
- That's good.
- Your quick thinking was great.
We visit a lot of places every week when we film the show.
I knew that it was just way too hot.
- You felt it right away.
- I sensed that it was too hot.
(His fingers suddenly move fast.)
It's tough for the staff and us too.
- They could pass out.
- Right.
Wait.
What is it?
What's wrong, Yeon Shik?
- Is it the opposite direction?
- What?
- No, wait. Seongdae Market?
No. This is the right direction.
- No, this is the right way.
- It's the right direction.
- It is?
- It is.
- This is going to Seongdae Market?
- Yes. It is...
- Hae In...
- Hold on.
I have a bad feeling about this.
- No.
- It's the right direction. Right?
I know Seongdae Market.
- Is this the right direction?
- If it's the opposite direction...
We're heading to Seongdae Market.
- Yeon Seok...
- Wait.
- This is the right direction.
- Right?
- Yes.
- The bus has to turn right here.
- It will.
- Right.
- It just did.
- It has to turn right.
The bus has to.
- They turn left on the other side.
- Let's press it.
- Is it the opposite direction?
- Seongdae Market.
- This is the right direction.
- Okay.
- I see.
- We're getting off at this stop.
- We're getting off here?
- Yes.
- I'm starting to feel dizzy now.
- You got scared for nothing.
- You gave me a good scare.
- Yes.
- Yeon Shik.
- I feel dizzy.
(Navi Yoo malfunctions due to the heatwave.)
I got a bad feeling for a second.
I'm suddenly sweating.
(This Stop, Seongdae Market)
- We're getting off here.
- Here.
(Staring)
"Boxing Club." Is that the place?
It's that way. It should be around there.
- I think that's the place.
- We can be there in three minutes.
- You have a sharp eye.
- I caught it.
(A boxing gym caught Jae Seok's eye.)
(I'm Dongjak-gu Fire Fist...)
(and want to give a boost to our champion...)
(Will the first Whenever Friend be at the boxing gym as expected?)
(They get off the bus.)
I think it's the boxing gym we passed by.
- That's the only boxing gym.
- There.
- The one on the second floor?
- Yes.
I think this is the building.
- Isn't it this building?
- It's right there.
- "Boxing Club."
- Yes. It's on the third floor.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Jeon Jin Man.
- That's the one.
(Dongjak-gu Fire Fists train here.)
- This is the place.
- It's here.
Hello.
- Ms. Yoon Na Ra? Thank you.
- Hello.
My gosh. You're the director.
- Nice to meet you.
Na Ra from the boxing gym wrote to us.
Hello.
- Are you Director Jeon Jin Man?
- Yes.
You are the former champion.
That's right.
Judging by your name,
I bet you were an infighter.
- It sounds like "Charge forward."
- Your name...
(Infighters tend to play aggressively.)
- There's no backing away.
- No backing away.
You don't look like an outboxer.
(He only charges forward.)
(Director Jeon Jin Man)
(There's no backing away for Jeon Jin Man.)
(WBO's last Asian Flyweight Champion)
(A championship belt)
(With his reputation as a champion on the line...)
How long have you been running the boxing gym?
- I've been running it for 13 years.
- For about 13 years.
Do you have a lot of members here?
- Most of them are longtime members.
- I see.
How long have you been training here, Na Ra?
I've been a member here for six years.
- That's a long time.
- And...
- I was on maternity leave.
- Okay.
So I've been training only for three years.
- Three years?
- Yes.
- Did you guys meet here?
- Right.
- I see.
Na Ra, what made you want to write to our show?
He's going to relocate the boxing gym.
He looked so stressed during the relocation process.
It's been really tough.
He said he lost 4kg.
- He's going to move his gym.
- He seemed exhausted.
I wanted to boost his energy.
So you're relocating your gym?
Yes. It's going to be in the new building...
across the street.
If it's in a new building,
- aren't you expanding?
- Yes, I'm expanding.
- You're expanding?
- Yes.
That's good news. Why...
But we've gotten attached...
- to this place.
- I see.
What a bummer.
I worry about the possibility I might end up with fewer members...
at the new place.
That's a genuine concern for you.
You're improving the facility.
But you're worried about the business side of the gym.
My gosh. So the director is expanding his business.
- They seem genuinely happy.
- Have you seen this before?
Have you ever met a genuine member like her?
- She wrote a letter to us.
- She did.
As for our members,
they don't take my coaching for granted...
even though they paid for my service.
They're always grateful for my coaching...
and try to take care of me.
So we bonded more deeply.
Where do you guys live then?
- Do you live around here?
- Yes.
When I was a newlywed,
the director lived in a house behind mine.
- Behind yours?
- So when I lived there,
I opened the window to clean the windowsill.
Then I saw him pass by.
I called him. "Director!"
Then I moved.
And Yeon Jung told me that she's his next-door neighbor now.
We really do live next door to each other.
The director drives a motorcycle.
When I see the motorcycle parked at the house,
I know that he's still home.
There was a time I glanced over at his house...
and came inside.
(She can check his whereabouts through the window.)
Then if you ever want to take a break from boxing,
you won't be able to.
- We'd run into each other.
- We...
(The reason behind long-term memberships is revealed.)
I'm sorry to ask you this, Na Ra.
But would you be able to show us some shadowboxing?
Could you and the director show us a few drills?
- Just briefly.
- Could you demonstrate?
- He can hold the mitts for her.
- I'm a bit shy.
But still.
All right, Na Ra.
(Dongjak-gu Fire Fist is ready.)
Now...
- Okay.
- Jab.
- My gosh.
- Two.
- Show them.
- She's good.
(Surprised)
(Screaming)
- One, two.
- She's good.
One, two.
- Double. Weaving.
- My gosh.
- One, two, three.
- Weaving.
Jab. One, two. Back.
One, two.
(Jaw-dropping)
- She's so good.
- She's great.
- Your combinations are impressive.
- Right.
Your form is great too.
- I can tell she's been training.
- What about you?
- Sung Tae.
- You played...
- I only trained for a month.
- a former boxer.
- But still. Try.
- I only trained for a month.
- He trained for six months.
- Gosh.
- Not me. Hae In.
- Hae In, you try it.
You try it, Hae In.
The director will help you.
(Cheering)
I think Hae In is going to be good.
- My gosh. This is...
- Well,
- Hae In also trained.
- Exactly.
You should've done it when we asked.
- It's been so long.
- Why are you doing that?
- To refresh my memory.
- He's weaving?
I don't want to get hit.
You what?
(Hae In puts on the gloves in no time.)
Hae In.
- Hae In.
- Gosh, this is crazy.
(Forming a fan club right away)
Jab.
- Two.
- My gosh.
- One, two.
- They're finding their rhythm.
- His form is showing.
One, two.
- One, two. Hook.
One, two. Hook.
One, two.
- One, two.
- Hook. One, two.
(Instantly turning it into a boxing drama)
You need to have the right chemistry with the director.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- You need the right chemistry.
- What about you?
- Try it.
- Come now.
Go ahead.
- Try it.
- You took boxing lessons.
- Try it. You practiced.
- All right.
- Try.
- Hey.
- Jab.
- Wait.
- How come...
- Jab.
- I'm not wearing gloves?
- Two. Jab.
- He's not even wearing gloves.
- Jab?
Exactly. Why...
- Gloves...
- Director.
You're not so kind to non-members.
You're nice to your members.
(Strict training on non-members)
- Right.
- Anyway, we're here today.
Since he's expanding his gym,
- Yes. Giving him useful presents...
- I hope we win him useful presents.
Right. I hope we win him a lot of presents.
Did you know? Hae In...
lived here for over 30 years.
- Over there.
- Me too.
- He used to live over there.
- I see.
- Really?
- You knew?
I see. They knew.
Wait. Didn't Han Ji Min say she also lived in Dongjak-gu?
- Right.
- Yes.
Didn't we win all the presents when Ji Min was on our show?
Ji Min was the Daughter of Dongjak.
- He's the Son of Dongjak.
- Son of Dongjak.
(It's time for the Son of Dongjak to perform.)
- The Son of Dongjak.
- Yes.
Let's check out Round One.
"Since the gym is expanding,"
"the fridge should step up a weight class."
"Samsung Double-Door Fridge."
(Round 1 prize: Samsung Double-Door Fridge)
- What?
- My gosh.
Wait.
- Wait. Round 1...
- Round 1...
(A major home appliance starting with Round 1)
- What?
- Round One's present is a fridge?
- The fridge at the gym is so tiny.
- You guys need one.
Come on. Don't say that.
- You guys totally need one.
- Right.
- It's so tiny.
- This is great.
- Gosh.
(Rally with Mitts)
(Sit 2-on-2 and use the boxing mitts...)
(to complete a 10-hit table tennis rally.)
- It has to be a rally?
- What?
- That sounds good.
- I see.
- Play table tennis with them?
- But they're curved.
Is it similar to the game we played with Hye Lyun?
It will be 2-on-2.
It has to be a rally?
Hold on. How should we do this?
We just have to hit the ball ten times,
- two-on-two.
- Right.
We're using the mitts instead of the paddles.
- So...
- We don't always have to alternate.
Everyone has to hit the ball once...
- during the ten-hit rally, right?
- Okay.
- Ten hits.
- This is doable then.
- It's doable.
- We just have to...
I think we can pull off a ten-hit rally.
But your bottom must stay on the floor.
- I see.
- Really?
- Wait. This is...
- Come on.
- And we have to serve like this?
- Yes.
- I see.
- You got it.
- This...
- Nice.
- We have to push it deep.
- This is so easy.
- They can do it.
- Nice.
- We have to push it deep.
- They can do it.
- I think they can do it.
- They got it.
- Don't push it too hard.
- Like this.
- Not too hard.
(Practice)
- Okay. We finished ten.
- I got it.
- Let's play just like this.
- Okay.
- Let's try it.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- We got this.
- I think we can complete Round One.
- Yes.
- Doing this...
- Let's go.
- Let's go. We got this.
- Okay.
- You got this!
- You got this! Yes!
- Let's go.
- We got this.
- You got this.
- You can do this, Sung Tae.
- Let's go.
- Here it goes.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
Okay.
- Two, three.
- Three.
- Four.
- Gosh.
- It's out.
- My gosh.
- Four.
- It's out.
- No.
(First try failed)
Come on.
- It's okay.
- Outside the line... It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- Wait. Will I bring down the team?
- Don't get nervous.
- We can't hit it until it bounces?
The ball has to land inside the lines.
It has to bounce first before we hit it?
- We can't hit it right away?
- No.
But that's allowed in table tennis.
- Even in table tennis, - No?
- it has to bounce first.
- Oh, right.
- This isn't tennis.
Sung Tae, just do what they tell you to do.
Okay? Stop...
- What's wrong with me?
- "Can't I touch it?"
"Can't I just hit it?"
- Let's do this. Right away?
- We got this.
- Let's practice.
- Should we practice?
- We should practice.
- Don't hit it too hard.
- Nice.
- There you go.
- Jae Seok.
Jae Seok is good at this.
Pass it only to Jae Seok.
I'm sorry.
Wait. Why are you trying to play offense?
- Sung Tae. It's a rally.
- We don't have to beat them.
- I'm in big trouble.
- It's a rally.
It landed right here.
- Sung Tae, we're not trying to win.
- No.
I was trying to give you a nice one.
I'm sorry.
We can do this.
It looks like you guys play table tennis.
- Yes. I'm all right.
- You're pretty good.
- We're pretty good.
- Round One...
- Let's try it.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
- You got this.
- We must pull it off this time.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
(We can do this.)
Set.
(2nd try)
Four.
Wait.
(It was out of bounds.)
Four.
Wait.
(Making eye contact)
Stop playing offense.
Wait.
(It's Sung Tae's fault again.)
- I thought I had to hit after you.
- It was out of bounds.
It could've gone to you. You could've hit it.
It would've been okay if I hit it.
- I'm a fool.
- Jae Seok could've kept playing.
(Blaming himself big time)
Hear me out. I keep thinking we're playing table tennis.
I just reacted out of reflex.
- I keep thinking I have to hit it.
- No.
- Whoever is closer should hit it.
- Give that to me.
- We should start it off.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Wait.
Only when it comes to my side.
- Mine.
- Hit it when it comes to my side.
- There you go.
- Mine.
(Practice)
- Nine,
- ten.
- Ten.
- Mine.
- We got it. That was fast.
- Then... Hold on.
- So...
- Sung Tae just has to stay back.
- He must hit it at least once.
- You have to play for both of us.
- Sung Tae...
Is it okay if he doesn't play at all?
- You must play at least once.
- Just once.
- Do what?
- You must hit the ball once.
- You must hit it at least once.
- Okay.
- Just once.
- It's our fourth try.
(The winning strategy is minimizing Sung Tae's involvement.)
- Just stay away from the ball.
- Fourth try.
- Let's go!
I bet my mom's going to love this.
(Laughing)
- Let's do this.
- Sung Tae the Fool.
I'm nervous.
Here we go. We'll play.
My gosh. Our rallies are moving so fast.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
- This is your fourth try. Ready.
- Okay.
Set.
- There.
- Mine.
There.
(He sends the ball over to Sung Tae.)
(I'll hit the ball only when it comes to my side.)
(If Sung Tae succeeds, they have a shot.)
Four.
(Disappointed)
- Gosh.
- Come on!
- Here.
- Gosh.
(Fourth try failed)
Wait.
- Come on!
- It was out.
(Chuckling)
Come on!
- Sung Tae.
- Sung Tae. Wait.
- Take your time.
- We should...
take our time.
(It's taking longer to complete Round 1.)
We were doing well during our practice.
Gosh, no. It's okay.
- We can practice. Let's try again.
- This is...
- Let's practice.
- This is an easy one.
I'm sweating like crazy right now.
- Wait.
- You haven't made any contribution.
Why are you sweating?
- I feel guilty.
- Sung Tae.
- Sung Tae. Let's switch seats.
- First of all...
Switch seats with me.
- Why don't you go over there?
- But...
Go over there.
- This is already our fifth try.
- Let's try this.
- Wait. This...
- Hold on.
- We're in trouble. This is...
- This is bad.
I thought we could complete Round Three after our practice.
This isn't easy.
- Wait.
- This is only Round One.
(His smile has faded away.)
This is bad. Seriously.
- Let's practice again.
- Let's try.
Do you want to serve?
(They're practicing again.)
- I'll serve.
- Okay.
Mine.
(Hae In is hitting the ball back every time.)
- It's going well.
- They got it.
(He's smiling again.)
Mine.
(Mr. Mine shows up when a crisis strikes.)
- We got it.
We're good as long as I don't play.
(Realizing it again)
Then do you want to just serve?
- Just serve.
- Yes. I'll do it.
- I'll just serve.
- Just serve.
- Practice your serve.
- All right.
- Practice.
- Let him practice his serve.
- Okay.
- That's good.
- This is perfect.
- This is our fifth try.
- Let's go!
You got this, Sung Tae.
- Ready.
- We can do this.
(They're on try number 5 just for Round 1.)
I'll be gentle.
Great.
Three, four...
(5th try)
five, six...
(Hae In returns the ball in a stable manner.)
Six, seven,
Mine.
(Fifth try failed)
- Their signals got mixed up.
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- Is it my fault again?
- Their signals got mixed up.
- I can't watch this.
- This is crazy.
This is crazy. I'm sweating.
- Hold on. This isn't a hard one.
- Six, seven, eight, nine, ten?
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten?
(Completing Round One is harder than it looks.)
We'll use our chance.
- Is it too early for that?
- On Round One?
- It's hurting my pride.
- This is...
This is so embarrassing!
How many chances do we get? Just one?
- Table tennis...
- But...
let us try one more time.
Let us try one more time before you use it.
- Just go for it. Don't practice.
- Okay.
- Don't practice. Let's go for it.
- There's no point.
Let's not practice.
- We were so close before.
- Let's go for it now.
- We can do this.
- We'll go for it now.
- Let's go for it right away.
- Hold on.
- Let's go for it.
- Let me put on the mitt.
- Let's go!
- We got this.
- Ready. Set.
(They're already on their sixth try.)
Mine.
(6th try)
- Three, four, - Mine.
Five, six...
(The rally is going smoothly.)
Six.
(6th try)
(Hae In hits it over.)
(They will complete Round 1 if Jae Seok hits it over.)
(6th try)
- You did it!
- Oh, no!
Jae Seok!
(The last return fails to go over the net.)
- Jae Seok!
- Jae Seok! That was the last one!
- What was that?
- The ball hit the inner part.
- Jae Seok!
It hit the inner part of the mitt.
- I can't believe this.
- No way.
I can't believe this.
Gosh, that was so close.
- That was so close.
- I can't believe this.
- Let's use the chance.
- Let's use it.
- We'll use the chance.
Let's use it.
(Chance)
- This is so fun.
- Gosh, we had nine hits.
- I'm sure...
- My gosh.
- You should pick one, Director.
- You should do it.
(There's 1 unlucky chance among lucky chances.)
- The Midas touch!
- Pick a good one.
- Hurry.
- Please read it.
(What is the chance the director picked?)
"This time, mitts will turn into paddles."
- I see.
- Paddles?
(Lucky: This time, mitts will turn into paddles.)
- Great.
- That's hard.
- This is better.
- This is way better.
Let's give it a shot.
- We need to practice.
- Of course.
We need to with the new gear.
- Are you good at table tennis?
- Yes.
- Table tennis...
- I'm also fine with basketball.
I've got no trust in you right now.
Okay.
(Practicing right away)
- It's...
- The ball flies too far.
- The ball flies farther.
- Right?
- Hit it gently.
- We should hit it lightly.
Just imagine touching it slightly.
Okay.
(Feeling out the paddles)
- Nice.
- Sung Tae, hold on.
You two have good chemistry.
Sung Tae, hold on.
That's it. Keep up the rally.
It doesn't matter since it's a rally.
The two of you can finish the game.
- That's right.
- Good.
Give it a go.
- Shall we try?
- Yes.
Stay calm.
Touch it lightly.
- Serve. Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Good luck!
- Let's go!
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(7th try)
- Mine.
- Four.
- That's it.
- Mine.
We've got it. Slowly.
- Yes, slowly.
- Keep going.
(7th try)
We have to succeed.
(Only Hae In needs to get the ball over the net to succeed.)
Set.
(7th try)
- Mine.
- Four.
That's it.
- Mine.
- We've got it.
Slowly.
- Yes, slowly.
- Keep going.
(7th try)
We have to succeed.
(Only Hae In needs to get the ball over the net to succeed.)
That's it.
Yes, slowly.
Only two need to rally.
(7th try)
(It was a clean-cut rally.)
Yes! We did it!
- We did it!
- It's a success, right?
(Cheering)
(It was a clean-cut rally.)
- We did it!
- A success!
- We succeeded!
- We did it, right?
- Yes, we did.
A success.
We did it.
- We did it.
I couldn't believe it.
Using the chance was a great idea.
We did it.
The rest doesn't matter after we each hit the ball.
All right. But here's the thing.
You have to decide whether to go...
- or stop.
- Tries 8, 9, and 10.
Right. The chance has been used.
- The tries are...
- Go or stop.
In one...
- Stop. Give them time to discuss.
- Wait.
We've only got a few tries left.
There are three tries left.
- Are you fine with losing that?
- Yes.
- You won't even get that.
- It's okay.
- Go.
- In one...
- In 1, 2, 3.
- We believe in you.
- Go!
- The second prize...
- We have to...
switch gears, don't we?
Here, Director.
"To keep the boxers' workouts healthy."
"LG PuriCare Air Purifier."
- An air purifier.
- It's an air purifier.
(LG air purifier for fresh air in the boxing gym)
(Round 2)
(The net gets higher.)
(Round 2: Foam rollers)
(There's a line behind them.)
Hold on, how is this possible?
Sit farther back.
I can't even see the line.
We should stand up.
We need to hit the ball higher.
For sure.
(Practicing first)
(Out of nowhere)
I think it's best to hold...
the mitt like this.
- Got it.
- Like so.
Don't hit the ball like this.
We shouldn't hit it like so.
- We can hit it back and forth.
- Okay.
- Point the mitt to the ground.
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
- You need to keep your butt down.
Sending it across isn't easy.
I can't see anything if I don't sit up a little.
Even Hae In gets angry.
- Hae In does get angry.
- Listen.
Just how? I can't even see the line.
At least let us kneel.
Controlling the distance is super hard.
- I'll cover this much.
- Okay.
- Mine.
Good. Is this a try?
- Practice.
- It's a try.
No, practice.
Is it not a try?
We're practicing.
Let's just go for it.
We did it. Come on.
- Let's go for it.
- What a bummer.
- If only it were a try.
- We can't mid-game.
Let's go for it!
You did it.
- All right. Just keep this up.
- Three tries left.
- Good luck to us.
- Good luck!
It's the 8th try in total and the 1st try of Round 2.
The eighth try.
- We can do it.
- Here we go.
Ready. Set.
(8th try)
Hold on.
(Hold on!)
- Hold on.
- Safe.
(8th try)
Hold on.
- Safe.
- Hurry.
(Eighth try failed)
Jae Seok.
My backhand isn't just working.
(Blaming it on his backhand)
- I just can't.
- The center.
Tries 9 and 10.
Nine and ten, okay?
Do I serve?
- Let's go.
- Here we go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
Let's give it a try.
- We can do it.
- Ready.
- Is this a try?
- Good luck.
- Let's give it a try.
- Yes, it is.
- We can do it.
- Set.
Here we go.
- Hit.
- Mine.
- Nice.
- That's it.
- Hit.
Hit.
It's out.
(Ninth try failed)
Really.
It's out.
(Quiet)
- The silence is...
- It's okay!
- Isn't it...
- Really.
- It's okay!
- How many tries are left?
- The last one.
- Serving is hard.
- Oh, my gosh.
It's... Let's practice first.
We're practicing. Here I go.
Practice is the key.
(Special training)
We only have one try left, right?
The least we should succeed is Round Two.
Oh, dear.
(Practice is the key.)
Like this.
- Jae Seok.
- It's just that...
- Hold on.
- That was too far.
- Let's practice again.
- Practice round.
- Let us practice again.
- One more time.
- Mine.
- That's it.
Always hit an underhand shot.
(Keeping at it until they succeed)
I'm sweating.
- That's it.
- Yes.
- Shall we give it a try?
Let's go. Good luck to us. The last try.
- The last one.
- Good luck!
- Let's do this.
- It's a try, right?
Yes. In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Let's give it our all.
Who's serving?
(The last chance to succeed Round 2)
- Should I?
- Yes, go ahead.
- If only I could...
- I'll serve it to you, Hae In.
- To you.
- hit it like this.
- All right. I'll be serving to you.
- Ready?
Okay.
Ready.
- Here we go.
- Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on the last try.)
(Last try)
- Hit.
- That's it.
It's over.
- Hit.
- That's it.
It's over.
- Hit.
- That's it.
It's over.
(Failed overall)
(Laughing)
(The last try ended without much of a rally.)
How fast.
(Recovering the fridge and air purifier)
- It's okay.
- Really.
- It's okay!
It's so cruel.
Gosh.
- We did well during practice.
- It's a big bummer.
- We're really sorry.
- Don't worry about it.
- How disappointing. If only...
- Thank you.
- Here.
We should've succeeded Round One fast.
- It's our show's clock.
- Thank you.
In your next gym...
- I'm sorry, Director.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
- We're sorry.
- No, it's okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
You did well.
- Great job.
- And in this heat.
Either way...
(Sad)
All right. The director...
is moving to a bigger gym,
so we hope many members come to work out...
and the gym becomes a hit.
- Thank you.
Whenever possible,
- there's no backing away!
- There's no backing away!
I hate this feeling the most, and the heat isn't helping.
I'm annoyed to the max.
My irritation level just shot up.
It's really irritating.
(Irritated to the max)
(Laughing)
- I...
- This is no joke.
Don't turn your back on the camera.
- So we're still shooting.
- Yes.
I thought we were on break.
- There's no break.
- Really?
- We need to get moving.
Let's go.
- Where?
- Where do we go?
- It's time to check.
- I see.
I've been...
on variety shows with Hae In every now and then,
but seeing him get angry was a first.
It was brutal. We couldn't even get off our butts.
(Cooling himself with cold water)
The spare time is 3:30pm.
- We have two hours to ourselves.
- Right.
- Lunch...
- We have Hae In with us.
- We can have lunch around here.
- Let's do that.
Shall we?
Do you know any places?
If you decide on a cuisine...
Korean cuisine, street food, or...
It's okay.
Whichever place you know is good.
- A place nearby.
- A place nearby?
Are you getting anything?
Or naengmyeon?
Sung Tae wants naengmyeon.
- It's hot.
- Something cold.
You've got nearby places saved.
- I do. This place is...
- He does?
Yes, it's around here.
This place is called Moss Kitchen.
- Is it open right now?
- Yes.
- Pork cutlet and buckwheat noodles.
- Yes!
- Buckwheat noodles!
- Nice.
- It's perfect.
- Hold on.
Break starts at 3pm.
- Let's just go.
- Hurry.
Shall we eat here?
You're not annoyed, are you?
- Let's go.
- Jae Seok?
- He was slightly annoyed.
- Right?
It's because of the heat.
This way.
- Earlier...
- At least it's not sunny anymore.
Great.
This is the kind of summer I remember from the past.
(A 7-minute walk to the restaurant)
(Calling someone)
It sure is a bummer.
Who are you calling?
- Reserving...
- He's making a reservation.
Hello? We're a party of four.
Can we get a table if we go now?
(Checking with the restaurant on the way)
We'll be there in about five minutes.
Hae In is...
the active type despite being prospective.
- Right?
- We went...
to a pork belly place nearby...
that Hae In knew.
He kept calling the owner ma'am.
Hae In is very affable.
He's lived here for years.
(As expected of Son of Dongjak)
- Turn right from here.
- Right.
(Navigation mode on after making a reservation)
It's way better than earlier.
Yes, turn left from here.
- We can make it across.
- We're almost there.
- Is there a table?
- Yes, I've checked.
(From showing the way to making a reservation)
Let's cross here.
(Even a short walk is sweltering.)
The old-fashioned red bean bingsu looks good.
Shall we grab that after?
- It looks good.
- Of course.
- As dessert?
- Yes, as dessert.
I'm in.
(Studying)
Where is he going? Is he making a reservation?
Where are you going?
I didn't expect a coffee shop to be here.
(Charging to the red bean bingsu)
Are you ready to order?
We'll be back in about 40 to 50 minutes.
- We close at 2pm.
- You do?
- We need to cross the road.
- Okay.
I only checked the business hours.
They close at 2pm. We can't have it.
- Are you really a Type P?
- Sorry?
I kind of do things on impulse.
He went inside on impulse.
- Does it close at 2pm?
- Yes.
Reserving...
(The guide acts unpredictably.)
Type P doesn't usually make reservations.
I was wondering why you went in there.
I thought someone you knew...
- was in there.
- No.
Does the coffee shop close at 2pm?
Can't she open it for longer?
(The guys want bingsu.)
There must be another...
Old-fashioned red bean bingsu looked good.
Hae In is searching for...
- red bean bingsu.
- He is, right?
I found one.
Cafe Atre.
(While the Dongjak-gu food guide is working hard...)
- Is it this place?
- Yes.
(They arrived at the restaurant.)
- It looks good.
- Right?
- Hi.
- Red bean bingsu?
- It's across the street.
Is that so?
The responsibility he has in his neighborhood.
- This way.
- Hi.
- I called you just earlier.
- A party of four.
(They got a table right away thanks to Hae In.)
- Hi.
I'm going to get cold buckwheat noodles and pork tenderloin cutlet.
- Something served fast.
- How about this one?
One assorted and one cheese.
- Yes.
- We can have loin, tenderloin,
- and cheese.
- I'm fine with any.
- We can taste all three.
- One of that.
- Four cold buckwheat noodles.
- Four.
We'd like...
- four cold buckwheat noodles.
- Four.
One assorted cutlet and one cheese pork cutlet.
Hae In is a regular.
- And three Diet Cokes.
- Were you a regular?
I will become one.
- He's got a sense of humor.
- Have you not been here?
It's a place I saved...
- to come one day.
- Saved?
- Today was the day.
- Is that so?
- Perfect timing.
- Today was the day.
- A local favorite.
- Yes, a local favorite.
(Excited)
The red bean bingsu...
The bingsu place is about 50m away from here.
We'd better grab that.
Is there a break time?
No, I checked.
- Okay.
- You're quite the planner.
- He's a lot more...
- A judger.
It's the heat.
- It's because of the heat.
- Hae In is a planner.
This place was introduced in "Live Info Show."
It has 1,200 reviews.
(The bingsu place)
- It looks good.
- The place is...
in the next alley.
- Cafe Atre.
- Okay.
He enjoys looking places up.
- Right?
- I do.
Yeong Ja's...
- Ultimate Food Map.
- The food map?
- Did you get it?
- Yes, and I was over the moon.
- Right?
- The must-eat food map?
It's in my safe.
I'm serious. The Ultimate Food Map.
- Is it on paper?
- Yes.
She had written down all the places in a sketchbook.
- For real?
- It's really thick.
Amazing.
- Yeong Ja must really...
- Seriously.
- adore Hae In.
- It's a treasure.
You can just tell the devotion she put into it.
- The sketchbook?
- Yes.
Any summer vacation plans?
None.
My shoot will start soon.
Which one now?
"Love Virus" with Sae Kyeong.
- Shin Sae Kyeong?
- Yes.
Hae In is all about romance these days.
- Love.
- Is it a romance drama?
Yes, it's really lovey-dovey this time.
- The upcoming drama?
- No action scenes.
- No action scenes?
- No.
Hasn't it been a while?
Yes, it's been ages since I've gone without fake blood makeup.
Not having blood makeup excites me.
Right.
How many siblings did you say you have, Hae In?
I have a younger brother.
- You're the eldest.
- You two are on good terms, right?
We're seven years apart.
- Seven?
- Yes.
- What does he do?
- He's my manager.
- Right.
- You know that famous photo?
- The umbrella photo.
- The power abuse.
- I remember. I heard about it.
- The justified...
- The justified power abuse.
- The one with the big umbrella.
- Like a beach umbrella.
- Right.
- Only because he's family.
- Yes.
The minion Mom made for me.
- "The minion Mom made for me?"
- Minion.
(Laughing)
That's funny.
- The minion Mom made for me.
- Is he here with you?
Yes, he is.
We're always together.
For your younger brother to go everywhere you do...
- It's tough.
- That's not easy.
We both need to put in the effort.
- Of course.
- Right.
He must know the most about you.
- For real.
- Yes.
It's great at times.
Like when?
Here's your assorted cutlet.
- Okay.
- Please place it in the center.
- My gosh.
- Enjoy.
Thank you.
The color is saying...
- it's extraordinary.
- Like sous-vide meat.
(Taking photos)
- Goodness.
- It looks good.
- Thank you.
- Incredible.
Bon appetit.
- Can we dig in?
- Amazing.
The color... Just how...
(Impressed)
- Thank you.
- It looks bomb.
The meat is super tender.
- Sung Tae, try it.
- Is it good?
- Okay.
- It's delicious.
How can such thick meat be so tender?
(Eyes widen)
For real.
- It's really good.
- Thanks to Hae In...
The meat is so tender.
I'm relieved it's good.
(Smiling)
Goodness, it's amazing.
How is it this pink?
This is bad. More people will come.
- Totally.
- Try this piece.
It's good.
(Proud)
(Relieved to see the guys enjoy it, Hae In finally takes a bite.)
It's good. The tenderloin is mind-blowing.
The tenderloin is incredible.
This place takes first place among all the pork cutlet places...
- Really?
- I've been to recently.
- This is the real deal.
- Right?
- For real.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- The green onion and wasabi...
are for the buckwheat noodles.
This sure is a must-eat place in Daebang-dong.
I was genuinely surprised.
Go ahead first.
- Dig in.
- The food is great.
It's so tender.
- Try it first.
- What?
- Okay.
- Good.
- It's so good.
- Totally.
No wonder you had this place saved.
- Not bad, right?
- No.
It's spicy, isn't it?
(Wasabi)
(Shuddering from the spicy kick)
I like wasabi, so I added the whole lot.
(Saving himself with cold buckwheat noodles)
(A refreshing taste that beats the summer heat)
It's good.
I want to bring my mom here.
It's a taste I want my family and friends to try.
(Proud)
Really, Hae In. This place is...
(A successful guide)
- For real.
- Really.
I'm all hyper now.
- You look different from earlier.
- I do, right?
I can feel warmth in your eyes.
Gosh.
(Warm)
I was all upset after failing earlier.
But my energy is back now.
It's thanks to Hae In.
It is.
What a relief.
We need to pay for our lunch.
- True. Hae In made the reservation, - We do.
But it's only fair for him to play the game.
Of course.
(No mercy when it comes to paying the bill)
- Why not add something in one cup?
- Sure.
You want to put something in it?
Place four cups,
- and whoever gets that cup...
- Should we mix it with wasabi?
It's been a while.
(You mean that strong stuff?)
- Really?
- Hold back,
and you're off the hook.
- Okay.
- Do we turn around?
- Yes.
- We'll mix them over there.
- Let's turn around.
- Okay.
(Turning back while the wasabi is mixed in)
What if you hold back like it's nothing?
I doubt you can.
(Don't worry.)
Imagine tears streaming down while you try to hold back.
- It's my first time.
- You can't hold back.
- They're all set.
- Here we go.
Let's pick together.
I'll take number one.
Only the number?
As long as we don't peek at it.
Let's bring it to the table after picking one.
- I'll go with four.
- Four.
What an ominous number.
- It's the number.
- Those who are willing to die...
shall live.
Those who are willing to die shall live.
- Two.
- I'll get it for you.
(Sung Tae, Yeon Seok)
- Here we go.
- Don't look at it.
You can tell with the lids off.
- Okay. We won't look.
- One...
- One, two, three.
(Drinking at the same time)
(Reading others)
I'm...
(Coughing)
Hey, Tae Ha.
Gosh. I couldn't help it.
(Inner shock)
(Trying to tough it out)
(Gulping)
(He couldn't bear the pungency.)
(Laughing)
Hey, Tae Ha.
Gosh. I couldn't help it.
You can't fight it.
- Look at him crying.
- Actually...
He closed...
- You can't fight it.
- That was crazy.
He closed his eyes gently.
- He's funny.
- First,
as soon as I uncovered it, I knew I was doomed.
I drank it all. But it's impossible to bear it.
Still, you're amazing.
- Are you okay?
- How could you drink it all?
Your eyes welled up.
- Hae In, that was hilarious.
- But...
- Gosh. It was funny.
- That was great.
- That was fun.
- It's funny that he got wasabi one.
- You're feeling even better.
- I'm much happier.
It's driving me nuts.
- Hae In sacrificed himself.
- It's great, isn't it?
- Thank you, Hae In.
- Thank you.
- I loved the lunch.
- Let's go now.
- The lunch is on me, then.
- Gosh.
- Thanks for the meal.
- He's treating us too.
- I'll come again often.
- Pardon?
I'll come here often. I live close by.
- Thanks for the meal.
- Thank you.
- Thanks. I'll come again.
- Bye. Thanks.
- Sure.
- Yes.
The weather's much better than before.
- You're right.
- Right?
- Yes.
- It's much better.
- We aren't under the scorching sun.
- It's better, but his stomach is...
(Burning with wasabi)
You're not going to end up in the ER, are you?
No, I'm fine.
(He needs to treat it urgently with bingsu.)
You should get red bean bingsu.
- I need it.
- He's doing a great job today.
Looks like he's trying so hard to endure it.
- But I love it.
- What do you like about it?
- It's lovely.
- Jae Seok.
Don't you love it? Hae In bought us lunch.
He found us a great place to eat.
- He got the penalty and paid.
- You loved it.
He made us laugh.
He made us laugh. So?
- We're almost there.
- Okay.
- Already?
- Yes.
- Hey, Hae In. You're amazing.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
We can turn left here.
- He's so...
- He guides us,
- so I feel so relaxed.
- Right.
I used to be with FNC Entertainment.
- You were the one doing this.
- Yes.
I was the Navi Yoo all the time. Yes?
- It's over there.
- Navi Jung is good too.
We're here.
- Wait, this is...
- Is this it?
- There are many people.
- Is it packed?
- It's full.
- It's popular.
Gosh. There is no seat for us.
- Please give me a second.
- We can't sit inside.
- Where is he going?
- Why does he...
- No, there's no seat inside.
I don't think there's a room.
It won't work.
(The older ones can sit at the table for two.)
(But he gives up in the end.)
- No, we can't go in.
- Can we wait a bit?
- That table is almost done eating.
- Let's go to a different place.
- Let's go.
- They're done eating.
- They are finished with theirs.
- There are other places too.
- This wasn't what I planned.
- But...
- First...
- This is a popular spot.
I think they will leave in a moment.
What about cup bingsu?
Sounds great!
- There's one up there.
- Let's go.
- Cup bingsu.
- Can't we wait for five minutes?
Hey, Hae In. You're crossing the road.
Where is he going?
- What's with him?
- No one can stop him.
- What? He's...
- What's with him?
- He's...
- Why does he do that?
He's almost flying around.
He's very proactive.
Hello.
- Could we order cup bingsu?
- Pardon?
- Can we order old-fashioned bingsu?
- Yes, you can.
Could you make four of those?
- They sell old-fashioned bingsu.
- I like this place.
- I want old-fashioned bingsu.
- The old-fashioned bingsu.
I'll have old-fashioned bingsu.
Thank you, Jae Seok.
You don't have to thank me. I'll gladly pay for it.
Thank you.
(After the big brother saved face, they sat to catch their breath.)
It's hot, isn't it?
I'm having a food coma.
I feel sleepy after having a great meal.
- Today, it's this hot.
- Yes.
But in the past, when it was cool,
- we didn't...
- Okay.
What is he doing?
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
They'll mistake us for forcing you.
- Hae In.
- Goodness.
We've come Dongjak-gu to be treated like royalty.
It's almost as if...
We've come to be treated well.
(The best guide in Dongjak-gu)
Hae In wants to show the best of Dongjak.
- Thanks.
- He represents Dongjak.
He's the son of Dongjak. Yes.
- And he's fast too.
- He's quick.
- He's really quick.
- "He's fast too."
- I'm serious.
- He's the son of Dongjak, indeed.
- Hae In is Dongjak's son.
- Yes, he is.
I thought this was "Running Man" for a second.
- He's on his feet right away.
- Exactly.
As soon as he saw cup bingsu across the street,
he sprang into action.
- I thought he lost it.
- I know.
"Why is he running all of a sudden?"
Actually,
it's nothing, but I bought cup bingsu.
Okay.
- It had to be paid in advance.
- Did you have to say it?
- I bought it in advance. Yes.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- So, keep your mouth shut and eat.
(Jae Seok buys the desserts as he's feeling better.)
- Because you're feeling good.
- Yes.
- It's already here.
- Thank you.
- Gosh.
Nice.
- Hold on.
- Gosh.
- Take that.
- It's on him.
It's on me.
(A rare chance of enjoying the bingsu that Jae Seok bought)
(Refreshing bingsu beats the heat.)
Be comfortable.
Come to think of it, this is the second episode.
We failed both times last week.
- We couldn't succeed at all.
- We have to succeed today.
We have to make it happen today. Seriously.
Let's go for it.
- Hae In.
- I'm a very competitive person.
As the son of Dongjak,
(Where is the 2nd spare time for them to have their 1st win?)
make it happen for us.
Good.
"Park Jin Wu."
"Doctor, architect, math teacher,"
- "firefighter, and a CEO."
- What?
"Friends with various dreams..."
"gather to clash and fall..."
- "for 1 second of dopamine."
- For 1 second?
"We want to spread this joy..."
"and recruit the ones to run with us."
"To run with us?"
"Please help us."
If it's one second of dopamine...
- Is it running?
- It's not running. Is it?
One second of dopamine?
- Running?
- Is it to get a faster time?
- They want to run together.
- That's the case.
- That's right.
- Are they runners?
They might be 100m sprinters.
- It's all thanks to you.
- Yes.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
- Gosh. It's Chung-Ang University.
- Gosh.
(Second spare time, Chung-Ang University)
For some reason, when I'm at Chung-Ang University,
- it feels familiar.
- It feels familiar.
We shot this program near this campus before.
Yes.
(Where is the spare time at Chung-Ang University...)
(with the mascot of the Blue Dragon?)
(Building 107, Room 105)
I think Building 107 is around here.
- Their buildings are numbered.
- Yes, they are numbered.
This is the Student Center.
- Isn't it Building 107, then?
- That's right.
I see. It's here.
Is it the Student Center?
It's Room 105 in Building 107.
- Room 105.
- It must be on the 1st floor.
Gosh. It's...
It says American football.
Yes, they are all here.
- They are a football team.
- An American football.
A football team.
(American football team)
(A mission related to football?)
This is bad.
You're having a day full of bad incidents.
- This is...
- He said this was bad...
- as soon as he saw football.
- This is bad.
He said, "This is bad."
I'd rather visit the scuba diving club.
- It's here.
- The scuba diving club.
- It's right here.
- Is this it?
It's here.
- Gosh.
The Blue Dragon.
It's a bit...
(Loud)
Park Jin Wu.
Jin Wu.
- Hello. Gosh.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
(Screaming)
- Hello.
- Gosh. It's crazy.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
(They're shocked to see the Whenever Friends.)
- Gosh. They're so fit.
- Gosh.
Hello.
- Who's Jin Wu?
- Hello.
He's the guest.
- Jin Wu, hello.
- Goodness.
First of all, because they play football,
- they're so fit.
- You're all so robust.
The room is filled with the smell of pain relief spray.
(The second Whenever Guest, Park Jin Wu)
You tackle one another with your bodies.
(Chung-ang University's football team, Blue Dragons)
(For a single touchdown, )
(they give it all on the field.)
(Chung-ang University's football team, Blue Dragons)
(The passionate youth on the field, Blue Dragons)
- I enjoy watching the NFL.
- Right.
But it's my first time meeting the players...
on a university football team.
What made you fall in love with football?
I got in after taking a year off.
I thought I should join a sports team.
I thought football was a sport I can experience only in college.
So I joined,
and I failed to leave the team.
You couldn't leave. You can join freely,
but you can't leave freely.
Once you're in, you can't leave.
I've been doing it for seven years.
Has it been 7 years? Have you been playing for 7 years?
- Didn't you graduate?
- I couldn't graduate.
He goes to an elementary school.
- He attends medical school.
- I see.
- Medical school?
- Right. He attends medical school.
- You go to medical school.
- When I read the letter,
- Right. There was a doctor.
- everyone had different dreams.
- One wants to be an architect.
- Right.
You're an architecture major. What's your major?
- I'm a business major.
- A business major.
- I dream of starting a business.
- That's your dream.
- I study medicine.
- You're a medical student.
- You attend medical school.
- I'm a math major.
- A math major.
- What about you, Ye Wan?
- I'm also a business major.
- A business major.
- What about you, Jun Su?
- Electrical engineering.
Electrical and electronic engineering.
More than anyone, you...
(His major sounds suspicious.)
He has an athlete vibe.
You seem to have worked out more than anyone.
- I'm an engineering student.
- I see.
- What about you, Jae Seung?
- I'm a philosophy major.
You're a philosophy major.
By the way,
you and Ye Wan,
compared to others,
are less tanned.
- I did get tanned.
- I see.
- But I put on lots of sunblock.
- I knew it.
He doesn't put it on.
(No sunblock)
Did you get a tan without any protection?
- You look cooler with a tan.
- I see.
- You should've put some sunblock.
- No way.
Your skin would peel off from sunburn.
- It does get peeled off.
- Right.
- But that's the fun of it.
- A skin disease.
It can happen. Really.
- Like skin cancer.
- It's dangerous and serious.
- You'll get sunburned. Yes.
- It's a big deal.
You look like you've been playing during the summer.
Yes. We've just come from Gangwon Province.
- From Gangwon Province?
- Yes.
We're training off-campus in Gangwon Province.
- I see.
- To shoot this show,
we've come for four hours.
How many players are there on your team?
We have about 20 players.
- About 20 players?
- Yes.
Because we don't have many players,
we don't have many substitution options.
So we have to keep playing even if we're hurt.
When I was a sophomore, I was lying down in pain.
And they said, "Hyo Seok, you're not hurt."
"You don't feel pain."
So I had to embrace myself and get back up.
We need to move up to Division One this year.
But once we made it up,
if we still lack players,
we won't be able to last in Division One.
Our team isn't well known.
In order to keep a team,
- you need more people to come.
- That's right.
I wanted many people to know about us.
New students have come in 2026.
- Were there new recruits?
- Yes.
- Ye Wan was the one.
- I was the new recruit.
- He's a new student.
- That's why I'm less tanned.
He's a new student from 2026.
(He's a freshman this year.)
You had your reasons.
Ye Wan, you are a freshman this year.
- It's only been a few months.
- Yes.
Compared to what you felt when you first joined the team,
how do you feel now? Has it changed?
- Think before you speak.
- Yes.
When I first joined the team...
- Outside pressure is creeping in.
- Come on.
- Don't do that.
- We're adoring him.
- Protect him.
(Reenacting the pressure)
They pressured him with a massage.
Does it suit you? How is it?
You should respond right away that it suits you very well.
- What are you doing?
- Come on.
Stop asking for specifics when you already know it.
That smile contained a lot of things.
- They're all his seniors.
- You know he's feeling uneasy...
right now.
You know that he's not in the state to speak frankly.
I think he's crying.
And he's sitting here out of all the seats.
Yes. That's the situation he is in.
I have a question.
Football is a rough sport.
Do you have a bench-clearing brawl like they do in baseball?
The game itself is a brawl.
They crash into one another.
- Yes.
- That's right.
There's no need for a separate brawl.
- We talk trash.
- We trade words too.
- You fight with your words.
- Yes.
We say, "Stop showing off."
I've never said it.
I've never heard such a thing.
You can say that.
After a crash, if I did it better,
I make eye contact before I go back.
Gosh. That's scary.
Is there any special chant?
There must be a chant...
to cheer you up before the game.
- One...
- We'll do it together.
- We should stand up for it.
- Captain will lead the chant.
- Do we have to get up too?
- Yes, let's do it together.
Wait. We're not part of the team.
Let's make a circle.
- Are we making a circle?
- Yes.
Before the game, we always...
Are we doing it too?
- Yes.
- Yes. Let's do it together.
We'll do the chant.
- Good.
- You can stand here with us.
One... We can do this.
Let's go.
How?
Like this.
Scream!
(What is this?)
(Chanting)
(Joining the chant)
(Screaming)
- Hey!
- Let's go.
Then we go to play after this.
Isn't this the chant by the natives in New Zealand?
- Gosh.
- I thought they were throwing up.
But what... What did you say?
I also had no clue when I was a freshman.
We didn't get it at all.
Ye Wan, did you know what he was saying?
Not really.
To recruit more players...
for your team,
you need to share the pros.
- As the youngest player, - Yes.
Why don't you sell the team to the new students?
- Me?
- Yes.
When you look at our Instagram account...
By the way, where am I supposed to look?
(He found the camera.)
When you look at our Instagram account,
you'll find many awesome photos.
You can see us playing the match too.
- Please join us.
- Good.
Many more should join the team so that Ye Wan...
- The youngest...
- That means less work for me.
That's right.
Hey, you shouldn't say that.
- Hey.
- Hey. You can't say that, Ye Wan.
- We don't give you any work.
- Hey.
Just say how nice we are to you.
(The youngest is getting loved forever.)
As time goes by,
- you'll remember this moment.
- Right.
You know. One day.
You'll go on with your path once you graduate.
Now, let's...
Let's begin now.
- Yes.
Please break the fortune cookie...
- for Round 1.
- For Round 1?
- I want to excel at it this time.
- Yes.
(They're desperate for a success in many ways.)
Gosh. Really.
- Gosh.
- What is it?
Ten Wilson footballs.
Good. Ten of these.
- Gosh. They are nice.
- It's good.
- Wilson is...
- Ten footballs.
It's a nice brand, isn't it?
- Yes.
- It's a great brand.
(Getting up)
The NFL.
(It's over 400 dollars in total.)
Each ball costs a lot, doesn't it?
- Gosh.
- Yes.
So, what's the game?
(Super Bowl Flip)
(Take turns bouncing the football...)
(to flip all the disc cones.)
(But the time limit is 30 seconds.)
If you fail,
you can start again from the first player.
(If anyone fails, they can start over.)
You have to be quick, then.
- If you make mistake...
- Can we do it again?
We can try it consecutively.
- We need to flip it by any means.
- Like ttakji?
- It's not easy.
- It makes a full turn...
- unless you hit it moderately.
- It's not easy.
- Does it?
- It's...
There's the right amount...
- of power.
- Exactly.
(It's all about controlling their strength.)
Why is every game so tough today?
I can't really do it.
- You can't do it like that.
- I think they'll fail.
- Right?
- It's so hard.
Gosh. That was too strong.
- When did I...
- This is it.
Gosh. We have to figure out the trick.
What is this?
It worked.
I see. I got it.
The right amount of strength.
This is the right amount of strength.
I got it.
- You just said you got it.
- Yes.
(Can't wait for Villain Heo's action.)
Look. I did it thrice in a row.
- You need to hit this part.
- It worked.
You have to go for the edge.
- I see.
- Yes. The edge.
- Go for the edge.
- Let's go.
This is it.
- Yes. I got it.
- This is it.
- I got it.
- I figured it out.
Let's go.
We can do it at once.
Okay. Our 1st try. In 1, 2, 3...
- Here we go.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(We have to succeed for this spare time.)
(1st try)
- You'll go again.
- You can go again.
Hit the edge lightly.
It worked.
I did it.
(Failed)
- I have to do it again.
- We start over.
- We have to start over.
- Are we starting over?
Start over. Aim for the edge.
- The edge.
- Okay.
The edge...
(Please...)
- Ten seconds left.
- Gosh.
I did it.
- Two.
- He did it.
(Succeeding 3 consecutive times with 6 seconds left)
He did it!
(We can succeed in one go.)
Gosh.
- Yes.
- We did it.
(They did it.)
(They succeed on their first try.)
(Screaming)
(Looking excited)
(A dramatic goal by Practice World Messi)
(Collapsing)
We did it.
What's wrong with him?
- Why?
- I'm dizzy.
- We succeeded.
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
- This is crazy!
This is crazy.
(Dopamine overload)
Okay. Round One, success!
(They succeeded Round 1 on their 1st try.)
- Wasn't there one second left?
- Gosh.
- It was because...
We failed so many times.
- But we succeeded in a row at once.
- It was in a row.
- Gosh. That was electrifying.
- Gosh.
Now,
we have nine tries left.
Are you going to go for it? Or are you going to stop?
Let's huddle up to discuss the strategy.
- Huddle up.
- Yes.
Let's take a timeout.
- A timeout already?
- We have nine tries left.
Do you even need to discuss it?
Why do you discuss it when we have nine tries left?
- Look at them.
- Do we go for it no matter what?
We have to go for it even if we fail.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- Okay.
Okay.
(A non-special strategy session ends.)
Go or stop? One, two, three.
- Go!
- Go.
The captain should pick one.
- Okay.
- Good.
"At our BBQ party, each player eats more than four servings."
- What?
- "Korean pork for 100 people."
(Present for Round 2, 100 servings of pork)
For 100 people?
- Look at that.
- What is that?
(Here are 100 servings.)
You can't finish that.
- It's 100 servings.
- We can finish it.
- No problem.
- It's 100 servings of pork.
Gosh. It looks good.
- Gosh.
- Gosh. It's real.
- Are you going back to Gangwon?
- Yes.
You can take it with you.
That's right. We can take it as is.
You can take it as is.
(Round 2)
(They'll have less time.)
(Round 2 is 20 seconds, reduced by 10 seconds.)
We succeeded with four seconds left.
- They can do it.
- They'll do it.
- We need to get the momentum going.
- We're doing great.
I think we can do it.
Hae In, do you want to go first?
- Should I?
- Go first, this time.
But I have a good feeling about this.
They'll succeed on this try, no doubt.
- On their second try.
- Okay.
It was...
It worked.
- Yes.
- I've found my specialty.
We're good.
(The three of them succeeded at the same time.)
I've found my specialty.
I've found mine too.
- I should've played rugby.
- That's it.
This is it.
Go.
I got it now.
Let's cheer up for Round Two.
One, two, three.
- Go!
- Okay. We can do it.
- Let's go.
- This is your second try.
- Yes. Here we go.
- Ready.
We'll begin now. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
Take your time. We have time. Go slow.
(2nd try)
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Darn.
- Back to the first player.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- Yes.
You have five seconds.
Gosh. We have to start over.
(They're back to the 1st player with 5 seconds left.)
- We have to start over.
- Do it again.
- Four, three, - Hurry.
Two, one.
(Failed)
(Yeon Seok failed at the critical moment.)
(Disappointed)
- It went pretty well, though.
- It did.
Why do I keep seeing the last nightmare?
It's okay. It's too early for that.
- Once...
- I get it now.
We start the game,
- we get nervous.
- You have to...
keep it closer to your body.
Hold on.
- It worked.
- You have to go lower.
- You're right.
- Go lower.
- Like this.
- Jae Seok, go lower.
- Hold on.
- It worked.
Try it.
(They both succeeded.)
You're guaranteed to succeed.
(Hae In figured out the trick.)
- They're flustered.
- They've got it.
- I got it.
- Let's go for it.
- Yes. I'll try it now.
- It has an 80 percent chance.
- Let's go!
- It's...
- Let's do it.
- Go.
- Let's go.
Give me some energy.
Let's try it.
- Should we go for it?
- In 1, 2, 3,
- here we go.
- Here we go.
- Do it gently.
- It's your fourth try. Ready. Set.
(4th try)
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Darn.
- Start over. Hurry.
Hurry.
- Darn.
- Why does it go so far?
(Failed)
(The failure zone)
Yeon Seok.
- Come on.
- Gosh.
- Give me a chance to try it.
- Three, two...
Give me a chance. Gosh.
(It landed on the shoes.)
We have to do it again because of the shoes.
Give us three seconds.
Why do you count down so fast?
I'm going to lose my voice.
- Should we change the order?
- But I got the idea.
Do you want to go first?
I think it's a good idea. You should go first.
- Okay. I'll go first.
- Okay.
- Yes.
We have an 80 percent chance of succeeding.
- I think we're good.
Do it gently.
- I have a 100 percent success rate.
- Gosh.
He's so good.
I'm always succeeding.
- Good.
- Okay. This is our fifth try.
We're still on Round Two.
- We have many tries left.
- It's a good time to succeed.
- Now...
- Let's do this!
- Go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
Ready.
Set.
- Okay.
- Be calm.
- Keep your posture.
- Darn.
I should set it in advance.
You have to wait for them to do it.
(Round 2, success!)
(They did it!)
(1 person is especially excited.)
(He can't control his excitement.)
Touchdown!
(Doing the touchdown ceremony out of nowhere)
- By the way, - We did it.
Sung Tae's screaming a lot.
(He gave his all.)
Then we have to go for Round Three.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Wait. How many tries do we have left?
We succeeded on our 5th try, so do we have 5 tries left?
- Yes. We have five more tries.
- Okay.
This is the last round.
- No.
- I think...
- You have to stop now.
- You still have a chance.
Think carefully.
This calls for a real discussion.
- You have to talk about it.
- Come.
I think they all get it now.
- We have to go for it.
- They get it now.
- It's 100 servings of pork.
- We have to get it.
- We have to go for it.
- It's 100 servings.
- Next time...
We still have a chance.
Gosh. I'm sweating so much.
He gave it all.
- Hae In is...
- It's the sweat of truth.
This sweat shows the truth. This is real.
Now, is the discussion over?
- Yes.
- Go or stop? You can stop.
Now, when you catch the ball,
tell us what you have decided between go and stop.
(He's ready to pass.)
- We'll go for it.
- Go!
Good.
- We can do it.
- This is crazy.
- Please read it, Jun Su.
- Shall we use the chance?
- What is it?
- Gosh. It's Oakley.
(It's crazy!)
"Stay in fashion while training under the scorching summer sun."
"Seven pairs of Oakley sunglasses."
(Present for Round 3: Oakley sports sunglasses)
Gosh. What?
(They're both practical and stylish.)
- We wear them and...
- Wear them in Gangwon Province.
Wear the sunglasses...
while you grill the pork.
- Smoke stings your eyes.
- You can eat right away.
They're perfect when playing sports.
(Become more stylish when playing, 7 Oakley sunglasses)
They're perfect.
(Round 3)
(2 disc cones are added.)
(The disc cones they have to flip have increased from 4 to 6.)
- Do we have the same time?
- Is the time limit the same?
We have 20 seconds.
But it's... Goodness.
Someone has to do it again.
The two with a higher chance to succeed...
- should do it twice.
- But the first player is crucial.
- Jae Seok should do it.
- You should start the game.
- Jae Seok and Hae In do it twice.
- I'll do it twice.
- We'll flip two cones.
- Yes.
You'll do one each, and we'll be done.
- Do you want to go fourth?
- Sure.
I feel no pressure.
We just need to do it again if we fail.
This is the best way to do it.
- Yes.
- This way.
- I place it.
- Like this.
- That's it.
Let's try it now.
- We can do it.
- Let's go.
One, two, three.
- Go.
Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 6.)
Calm and steady. Okay.
(Failed)
It's okay. You're the first player.
(6th try)
- I did it.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Take your time.
- He did it.
- Okay. The last one. Slowly.
- Five, four...
(Failed)
- One.
- We have to start over.
- Okay.
- We were almost there.
(Sixth try failed)
(We were so close.)
- We were almost there.
- Okay.
- We saw the potential.
- We were almost there.
(Disappointed)
- We got this.
- We were so close.
He got nervous. That's all.
Don't feel too much pressure.
Hey, Sung Tae.
It's okay.
(Trying hard to comfort him)
The last one always feels the pressure.
(Resenting)
I'm serious.
The last one feels the pressure.
- I just did it.
- Did you see it?
(He's unable to speak.)
- I didn't want to do it.
- You felt the pressure.
It was as if he were pushing the button for a time bomb.
You get nervous when they count, "5, 4, 3, 2, 1."
He was like, "Do I cut the blue cord?"
They count down on purpose.
Gosh. This is crazy.
- Did you see that?
- You're good.
- Stop it.
- I was really good at this.
I succeeded continuously.
Look.
(He acted cocky in the past.)
Go at a 45-degree angle here.
Gosh. People can't help but be nervous.
I wondered why they did that when I watched them on TV.
For goodness' sake.
Good.
I'm breaking out in a cold sweat.
But this is...
We can't fail this one.
Let's go.
Let's do this!
- Yes!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 7.)
We can do this.
- Gosh.
- This is your seventh try.
- Ready. Set.
- Yes.
Nice.
- Nice.
- Okay.
(Failed)
- We still have time.
- Take your time.
- Go slowly.
- This is our last chance.
- We can do it.
- It's okay.
- Succeed consecutively.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- Start over.
- Go slowly.
- Five,
- Darn it.
- four, three,
two...
Okay.
Let's use the chance.
- Timeout.
- We'll use the chance.
- Let's use the chance.
Once you get stuck, it's hard to get out.
I'm nervous.
- It's better than before.
- You're sweating.
- Pick the good one.
- This one?
Pick a good chance.
He picked the best one.
- We get one additional try.
- Okay.
(Lucky! You get 1 bonus try.)
- Thank you.
- Good job.
- We have a free try, then.
- Yes, we do.
We won't count this try, then.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- I feel a dopamine rush.
Nice.
Yeon Shik, you should go first.
- Should I?
- Yes.
- Do I flip two cones?
- We'll get lucky.
Okay.
Just do it as you practiced.
You can just do it casually.
- I'll go for it casually.
- Ready.
- Casually.
- Set.
(Lucky Chance Round)
Casually. Darn it.
(Chance Round)
- Casually.
- Yes. That's it.
- Good.
- Okay.
- He did it.
- Great.
- Okay.
- It worked.
- Good.
That's it.
Go.
- Go.
- That was good.
(Failed)
Start over.
(No!)
Calm down and do it slowly.
Start over. We don't have time.
- Okay.
- Five,
- Do it.
- four, three,
- Darn.
- two...
- That was good.
- Nice.
(Crying)
- Good.
- Nice.
Good job. You did great going first.
Good. The 1st and 2nd players were great.
Hey, Sung Tae!
- That spot...
- The last spot is...
Hey, Sung Tae!
- Well...
- Can you handle the last spot?
This spot is quite tough.
- That spot...
- The last spot is tough.
You did well during practice.
- You're doing really well.
- That's it.
- All of a sudden?
- He's another Practice Messi.
- Like that.
It's because he's fainthearted like me.
Right.
- He plays many villains, - Right.
- He's fainthearted.
- but he's fainthearted.
He gets anxious.
- Please!
I'll make sure to make it.
(There aren't many tries left.)
Give them some energy.
- Chung-Ang University energy!
- Hey!
Gosh!
- All right. Here we go.
- It's the eighth try. Ready.
- Tap.
- Set.
- There you go.
- Tap. Gosh!
- It's okay.
- All right. It's okay.
- Tap.
Gosh. Take it slow.
Take it slow.
- Gosh!
- Hold on!
- Gosh! Yeon Seok!
- Don't do that!
- Yeon Seok!
(Where are you going?)
- Don't do that!
- Yeon Seok!
- Don't do that! That's not it!
(Eighth try)
- That's not it!
- Gosh!
- Hey!
- One more time.
- Gosh.
- You have to...
(A massive failure)
- Gosh.
- You have to stop it first.
- Come on!
- Gosh.
- You have to stop it first.
- Goodbye, sunglasses.
- Come on!
This guy...
They will come into my pocket.
Look at this guy.
Move to the last spot.
Hae In, move to number one.
- You should move to number 1.
You should move to number one.
(He naturally tosses spot number one to the younger one.)
We have two tries left. We have to do this.
It won't make sense if we don't make this.
We can't be like this.
- We will fail two weeks in a row.
- That can't happen.
Hit the bottom hard.
- Tap.
- I must not get worked up.
- I'm doing so well right now.
- It has to get pushed forward.
I must not get worked up It has to get pushed forward.
- Gosh, this is crazy.
Push forward.
It can't be too strong, Yeon Seok.
- It should be this much strength.
- Gosh.
- Right, Yeon Seok.
- He's talking to himself.
- Self-control.
- You're good at this.
Yeon Seok! You can't be like this!
This happened earlier,
but it was sad to watch you move forward.
(It was sad to watch you.)
- Yeon Seok.
- Gosh.
Gosh.
- Why would you bring that up?
- That was close.
Well...
- I was in a hurry.
- Right. You were in a hurry.
- It's understandable.
- I was rushing myself.
- Right.
You lost your head earlier.
- I couldn't handle it.
- Right. You lost your head.
You lost your head. But Sung Tae was the only one...
who didn't laugh at you.
(Serious on his own)
He was the only one who didn't laugh.
- As he could relate.
- Right. He could relate.
- Sung Tae didn't laugh.
- Gosh.
- This isn't easy.
- Let's do this.
- We can do this!
- Let's go!
- Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 9.)
- Tap.
- This is it.
- It's okay. Take it slow.
- Take it slow.
(Ninth try)
- Why can't I do it?
Take it slow.
- Tap.
- Take it slow.
(Ninth try)
- Tap.
- There you go.
- One.
- Gosh.
- Come on.
- We can do this.
- We have time.
- Five,
- All right.
- four, three, two...
(Ninth try)
(They fail with their ninth try.)
Gosh.
- It's okay!
There's one try left.
(There's only one try left.)
It's okay.
- It's okay!
- Okay!
- It's the last try.
We have to stay calm. We're rushing it.
Why am I sweating so much when I didn't do anything?
Why do you feel so warm?
(Blazing)
- This is driving me crazy.
- Well...
(They're crazily desperate to make it happen.)
We can't fail.
They need to have some meat after practicing in the sun.
- We have to do it this week.
- We can't fail.
- We will fail two weeks in a row.
- That can't happen.
Let's do this. Let's flip our cones even after making it.
- It's to save time.
- Right.
You get me, right? The next person might fail.
- Okay. Without being unprepared.
- Right.
- The ones who are done.
- But is that allowed?
- Let's do that.
- That won't matter.
- Right. They made it anyway.
Okay.
We have to make it happen. Why worry about that?
Why are you telling me off?
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh.
You seemed to be in a good mood just now.
It ruined my mood all of a sudden.
- You've lost your head as well.
- It ruined my mood all of a sudden.
- Let's do this.
- Gosh.
- Let's go!
- This is so stressful.
Gosh.
(Many have their moods ruined after failing consecutively.)
We were doing great.
- Let's go!
Let's go!
- Here we go.
- Ready.
Set.
- Tap.
- Okay.
- Nice!
Tap.
It's okay.
(Last try)
Tap.
(Failing)
(Last try)
- Tap.
- There you go.
Done.
Please!
- Take it slow.
- Five, four,
Please!
- Take it slow.
- Five, four,
- Five, four...
(It's Sung Tae's turn with 5 seconds left.)
- Please!
- Take it slow.
Four...
Four,
- three, two...
- Gosh!
(Last try)
(Failed overall)
Heo Seong Tae!
- Three, two...
- Gosh!
Heo Seong Tae!
(Wailing can be heard throughout the room.)
- Gosh!
- No!
- Don't leave us!
- After this...
- Oh, no!
I was thinking about having 100 portions of meat.
(They couldn't pass the wall of Heo Sung Tae.)
It would've been tougher to end it like this.
Gosh, it's like a moving company is here as there are so many prizes.
- Right. It's empty now.
- There were so many things.
- It's okay!
- Sung Tae!
Sung Tae!
(Grabbing tightly)
(Just the sound of wailing can be heard.)
You have to head out again, right?
- Right.
- We must go.
It was a midsummer night's dream.
- Let's go and train.
- Right.
We'll grab a meal afterward.
Send me the captain's bank account number.
I'll send you some money right away.
I'll get you 100 portions of pork belly.
(That's against the rules.)
- That's great!
- Gosh!
(The merch and clock are the only things that can be given.)
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry!
I love it!
Gosh, this is how it ends.
(Full of regret)
- Sung Tae...
- Gosh.
- He's sweating.
- He's sweating so much.
I didn't know how things would end,
but I wonder if we should've changed his spot.
- I still hoped that...
- He should've felt the joy...
- of overcoming it.
- Sung Tae would get it done.
Right. We hoped that he would overcome his pressure.
(We hoped that he would overcome his pressure.)
How did I fail to do that?
(He failed to overcome the pressure.)
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
I did so well during practice.
- But...
- This is so cruel.
As a big fan of Whenever Possible,
I was able to experience with my own sweat...
that this was a real variety show.
I'm a villain in the show.
Please curse at my mistake today...
and enjoy the show.
Thank you.
"Our Sticky Love."
Please show us your support.
(Please show your support for "Our Sticky Love.")
(The one who makes Jae Seok's veins pop out.)
(Today's Whenever Friend, Cha Tae Hyun)
(He appeared in every season.)
(He passed Round 3 every time.)
(I'm the pig head of Whenever Possible.)
(The Whenever Friend with experience)
(Tae Hyun has come with a new face.)
(Second Whenever Friend, Jin Ki Joo)
(She has been teaching students a lesson.)
(Clever and brave Ki Joo)
(Screaming)
(Grab it!)
(Hit it!)
(Gosh, this isn't easy.)
(Ki Joo isn't the athletic type.)
(Ki Joo might not be athletic, )
(but is she lucky instead?)
(Lucky and energetic Tae Hyun and Ki Joo's...)
(endless flow of luck)
(Whenever Possible Season 5)